I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are the seven pints I made
this week. Started it off by recreating
Ben & Jerry's chocolate therapy flavor.
This was a chocolate pudding ice cream
with Oreos mixed in. Then I did a
special viewer request baked Alaska,
which was another Ben & Jerry's
recreation. This came from the flavor
graveyard. It was a vanilla ice cream
with a white chocolate swirl and
marshmallows mixed in. Then I recreated
Dairy Queen's caramel craze blizzard.
Vanilla ice cream with peanut butter
cups, caramel cups, and a chocolate
swirl. Then I made what is supposed to
be milk bars, cereal milk ice cream. I
used Captain Crunch to flavor the milk
and then made the ice cream with that
milk. This was just delicious. Then I
did Ben & Jerry's peanut butter cup. So
peanut butter ice cream with peanut
butter cups on top. This peanut butter
base is to die for. The texture is so so
good. You guys have to try it out. I
guess fall starts in August now, so
people wanted me to make a pumpkin spice
recipe. So, I did a pumpkin spice latte.
Of course, it was banging. And then I
ended off the week with a caramel
chocolate cheesecake ice cream. This is
another Ben & Jerry's recreation. This
recipe will be out in a few days, so
stay tuned for that. Follow for more
recipes and comment flavors you want to
see